When I throw a jab or a straight,
it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart,
I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me,
take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything,
I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
Junichiro's Promise
"Junichiro's Promise."
What was your reason for getting so strong?
I just wanted to catch up to the
big back I saw in front of me.
I first met her ten years ago,
the day after I moved here from Tokyo.
A-hup!
You just moved in yesterday, right?
Where'd you come from?
Tokyo.
Tokyo?!
Isn't Tokyo the place with
all the big, tall buildings,
where everybody lives way up high?
Did you, too?
Yeah.
That's so cool!
Oh, and all the cars float in the air,
and there are giant robots
walking around, right?
Yeah, sure.
That's awesome!
So, is that fun?
Lemme see it for a sec!
Hey, stop—
Don't break it! Don't you dare break it!
Don't worry!
2 Minutes Later
How does that even happen?!
I guess I had a kinda hard grip on it—
Wh-What did I just do?
That's not enough.
Huh?
I broke something that was important to you.
Hit me a hundred more times!
I won't feel better until you do!
I-It's fine...
You're sure just one hit is enough?
I'm sure!
Well, now I owe ya one!
I'm Tomo. What's your name?
It's... Junichiro...
Oh, yeah?
Nice name!
Greetings!
You must be Junichiro.
Y-Yes, sir!
I am terribly sorry!
Huh?!
My Tomo caused unspeakable trouble for you.
The kid actually went and
told him what happened?
A big, scary dad like him?
As Tomo's father, I will naturally
pay for all damages caused,
but is there anything else I can do?
No, really, everything's fine now.
That does not placate me!
They're definitely related!
Hey, Goro! What are you doing?!
Akemi!
Don't terrorize the new neighbors!
They just moved in!
Um...
Why are they behind me?
I'm sorry about that.
These idiots of mine are
bothering you, aren't they?
I-It's okay...
All right, come with me!
I'll settle this with his
parents myself later.
Be sure to make up with him, okay?
Okay.
I'm really sorry I broke your game.
We're the same age, and we live next door,
so I'd really like to be your friend.
Can I?
That's... fine with me.
From then on, Tomo and I played
together almost every day.
You've gotta be crazy!
Hey, gamer kid! Aren't you
gonna come outside today?
Do I look like I can go outside?
And stop calling me a gamer kid.
Well, you never call me by my name, either!
It's always "Hey, you," or "monkey,"
or "idiot," or something!
Sorry.
Okay, then... Tomo.
Say it one more time!
Huh? T-Tomo...
For some reason, it makes me really
happy when you call me by my name!
Why is that?!
This can't be right... This can't be right!
Hey, Jun!
Mind if she plays with us today?
This is Misuzu. We've been friends forever.
Be her friend too, okay?
She looks like a doll.
So you're Junichiro?
I hear you came here from Tokyo.
Th-That's right.
You have the face of a bumpkin, though.
Isn't she hilarious?
She'll pick a fight with anyone!
That's not hilarious!
I've never gone out to catch bugs before.
What kinds of bugs can we catch?
We have stag beetles and rhinoceros beetles.
Really?!
I don't wanna go to any
more weird places, though!
No climbing cliffs or crossing rivers!
Don't worry!
We'll catch our bugs at the
top of these stairs today.
It's only about two hundred steps.
Is this kid some kind of monster?
Wow, he's sure fired up!
What a child.
T-Take that!
I got here first!
That was awesome!
You look pathetic.
In the end, the one still
standing is the winner.
I'm gonna make you cry like a baby later!
You guys are such good friends already!
Look, Jun!
I found a big one!
Wow, a giant stag beetle!
That's just a giant cockroach.
Gross.
Awesome! I've never seen
one like this before!
These sell for thousands in stor—
Beautiful!
Hey, you finally get it now, too?
What's with this girl?!
Look, Tomo!
I got one, too!
Hey, nice!
It looks so cool!
Hey, so you can smile!
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Well, you're always making
those sulky faces.
See? Playing outside every now
and then isn't so bad, right?
Well, every now and then...
Come on, hurry up!
You've gotten pretty good at climbing trees!
A little climb like this is nothing.
I can't call you a gamer kid anymore!
That's right! Never call me that again!
I was finally able to keep
up with Tomo's crazy games.
Somehow, just being with Tomo
made me feel like I had gotten stronger.
But that was just...
Hey!
That's a pretty cool thing you've got there.
...a big misunderstanding.
Hey...
What happened to your cheek?
Huh? Oh... I just fell.
You're a real klutz, aren't you?
Yeah, I sure am! I gotta be more careful!
What are you laughing about?
You're so confusing.
Here ya go.
Why did you have this?
Oh, well...
I found it lying on the ground!
What?!
What were you thinking?!
You got it back alone?!
Hey, hang on...
Why would you take a risk like that?!
What do you think you're doing?
Why do you do things like this?
Huh?
I never asked you to get it back for me!
I dunno what you're talking about,
but if you're having trouble with something,
of course I'm gonna help you.
We're friends, aren't we?
Don't make it sound so simple!
I can't do anything like that for you!
Here.
You can borrow it.
Really? You're sure?
Yeah.
Thanks!
How long can I borrow it?
Until...
Until I'm a stronger man than you.
When that time comes...
I'll take it back!
Aizawa Dojo
How much stronger you get
from now on is up to you.
I won't go easy on you.
Yes, sir!
Please teach me!
You will respond with "Osu"!
O-Osu!
It's really been ten years?
And I still...
Yes! I beat the game!
How many dozens of times does that make now?
When's he gonna come to take this thing back?
He's already way stronger than me.
When Tomo Puts On
a Swimsuit...
"When Tomo Puts On a Swimsuit..."
We're here.
Heya!
Hey!
We all decided to go to the beach
together over summer break.
Hey, you're supposed to inflate
the swim ring after we get there!
So you really came? I thought you
had no interest in the beach.
I wasn't intending to come...
Well, you got a new swimsuit.
Now you don't have to be shy about
going to the beach with Junichiro.
Yeah, but I don't know if I have the guts
to play around with him in this swimsuit.
Want me to go with you?
You'll come with us?
Carol, please.
I bet Jun-kun's face when he sees Tomo-chan
in a swimsuit will be amazing.
...but I'm looking forward to this, Junichiro.
To what?
This is for you, Jun-kun.
Hey, cut it out!
Carry the parasol, too.
Why do I have to—
And wear these.
H-Hey, you guys...
He looks like that one guy in the group
who's fired up when no one else is.
You're a bit too excited, Junichiro.
Calm down, Jun! There, there!
It's...
...the...
...beach!
Woo-hoo.
Yeah!
Thanks for waiting, Jun-kun.
Where's Tomo?
Why are you looking up?
Shower Room
Changing Room
Entrance
Woman
Tomo's hiding over there.
What're you hiding for?
Jun!
You're not supposed to be wearing a hoodie.
Take that off and let's go swim—
C-Can't breathe...
Yay!
This is the best!
Feels so nice.
It's unusual for you to
come over to me by choice.
Shut up. There's just nowhere else I can sit.
So Carol and Tomo are too
much of a temptation,
but being around me doesn't
bother you at all?
Let me hit you just once.
I didn't even say anything.
Hey, Jun!
Why are you sitting down?
T-Tomo?!
Let's hit the water!
Come on, hurry up!
W-Wait, you idiot! Don't cling to my arm!
Why not?
Stop! Get away!
She's enjoying the beach so much,
she forgot about the swimsuit.
Come on!
Tomo! Please!
Tomo, you probably haven't noticed...
But you're being just the right
kind of aggressive right now.
Gah!
What's wrong?
Like, Aizawa Tomo and the
blonde boob chick are here!
F-For real?!
Take that!
Whoa... She's pretty
impressive without clothes.
I, like, wouldn't ever
want to stand beside her.
You said it.
Like, who are you?
Jun-kun! Jun-kun!
Don't get close to me!
Was splashing around always that painful?
Anything is a weapon in her hands.
Anyway, why does Jun-kun keep running
away from Tomo-chan and me?
He's fine around you.
You don't actually know what
you just said, do you?
It's this.
Do you mean Jun-kun doesn't like boobs?
No. The opposite.
He's a pervert who loves big boobs.
I don't get it.
Man, the beach really is fun!
Hey, you there!
You're a cutie!
A-Are you talking about me?
Yeah, you! I'm talking about you!
That's the first time a guy
I don't know ever said that to me!
Huh?
What did you see on me that made
you think that? Tell me in detail!
Okay, okay!
I'll tell you everything.
Around those big rocks over there...
Where we can take our time.
Wait, I'm kinda... scared.
C'mon, let's get moving.
H-Hang on!
Wow, you're strong!
I wanna slug him into orbit right now!
Hey, chill out.
But I can't!
I don't think I could hold back!
Are you being shy?
That's part of what makes you cu—
Huh?
Wh-Where did you come from?!
You her boyfriend?!
Huh? No way.
Then why'd you get between us?!
I don't really know why,
but you're just wrong.
Don't touch Tomo with your filthy hands.
I wish he'd say that one more time...
One more time... One more time...
Sorry. I shouldn't have butted in.
Huh?
You wouldn't want people thinking
I'm your boyfriend, right?
I wouldn't?!
What's wrong with this idiot?!
Does it bug him that much to have
people think we're a couple?!
Wouldn't
Want
Jun-kun! Help!
Jun?
What are you doing? Let's go.
Thanks!
Who the hell are you? Her boyfriend?
My boyfriend, he said!
Go ahead and think that if you want.
I can't be bothered with you.
Wh-What?!
He wouldn't want people thinking
he and I are a couple?
But she's fine?!
Isn't that a good thing?
Like hell it is!
If you really want to change
the way things are,
today's your best chance to do it.
It is?! Wh-What should I do?!
Get as close to Junichiro as you can,
and always stay within his line of sight.
That's it?
That's it.
Soft Serve
Jun! I bought us soft serve!
Really?
Yep! It's on me. Eat up!
Thanks.
Is this getting close enough?
Closer, maybe?
Is this really all I need to do?
He's not reacting at all.
Tomo... What's gotten into you?
Whoa! That's cold!
Oh, sorry.
It's fine. I'm getting back
in the water later, anyway.
Huh? Something wrong?
Uh... Nah, nothing.
Let's get in the water again!
S-Sure...
Something's been a little
off with me lately.
There were all kinds of things
I wanted to do with Tomo today,
but every time she touches me...
Every time she smiles at me...
I suddenly can't move.
Why do you look so smug?
You didn't seem like you were having
much fun at the beach today.
Did something happen?
Huh? No, not really...
Actually, maybe something did happen.
I knew it. I'm still not sure
what it is he wants to do,
but he doesn't see Tomo as
anything but a girl anymore.
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love